

Dang Quyet Tien

Technical Lead

Date of birth: Dec 04, 1991

Gender: Male

Phone: 0349.819.299

Email: quyettien.ictu@gmail.com

Address: Hanoi, Vietnam

Website: https://softviet.net

OBJECTIVE

I'm a software engineer with an appetite for complex problems. I'm easy going & take responsibility for my work and I would like to become a CTO in the near future. So, over the last 6 years, I have developed a wide range of websites with many technologies such as Django, Reactjs, Nodejs, Next.js, React.js, Vue.js, Nuxt.js and develop mobile applications with React Native. Build systems with Kubernetes, Rancher, Docker, Docker Swarm.

EDUCATION

Sep 2009 - July 2014 Information and Communications Technology University

Major: Software Technology

Degree: Good

WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2020 - Present	VuCapital LLC - Team size: 10 members - Position: Technical Lead
July 2017 - March 2020	MOBILE HEALTH - Team size: 6 members - Position: Backend Developer & DevOps Engineer
June 2014 - 2017	SAMSUNG VIETNAM MOBILE CENTER (SVMC) - Team size: 15 members - Position: Backend developer and DevOps Engineer
Aug 2013 - Feb 2014	SOLID - Team size: 3 members - Position: Team leader
Aug 2012 - Aug 2013	DCOS - Team size: 8 members - Position: Developer

CERTIFICATIONS

SKILLS

Language	English, Vietnames
Programing Language	Python (Django), React.js, React Native, NodeJs (Sails.js), Vue.js, Nuxt.js
DevOps	Git, Perforce, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Docker, Docker Swarm, Microservice, Ansible, Terraform, Packer, Fastlane, Fabric

INTERESTS

I like to explore new technologies

PROJECTS

Ontiva

(2020 - 2020)

Customer	VuCapital
Description	Youtube downloader
Team size	10
My position	Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Use Docker, Ansible, Packer, Terraform to build the server system Manage team.
Technologies used	- Nuxt.js, Django - Docker, Ansible, Packer, Terraform

Mp3download

(2020 - 2020)

Customer	VuCapital
Description	Youtube to Mp3 converter
Team size	10
My position	Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Use Docker, Ansible, Packer, Terraform to build the server system Manage team.
Technologies used	- Nuxt.js, Django - Docker, Ansible, Packer, Terraform

Evano

(2020 - 2020)

Customer	VuCapital
Description	Video and audio editing software online
Team size	10
My position	Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Use Kubernetes to build an auto-scaling system Manage team.

Technologies used	- Next.js, Django - Kubernetes, Rancher
-------------------	--------------------------------------------

Uptra - Cross Promotion

(2019 - 2019)

Customer	Vala
Description	a Shopify application.
Team size	5
My position	Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Develop API for the client application
Technologies used	- React Js, Sails.js, Docker

Busio by FITi

(2018 - 2018)

Customer	FITi
Description	a Shopify application.
Team size	5
My position	Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Develop API for the client application
Technologies used	- React Js, Sails.js, Docker

Chatative by FITi

(2018 - 2018)

Customer	FITi
Description	a Shopify application.
Team size	5
My position	Team leader & Technical leader
My responsibilities	- Develop API for the client application
Technologies used	- React Js, Django, Docker

Manadr

(2017 - 2018)

Customer	Mobile Health
Description	This app allows patient connect to doctors.
Team size	25
My position	Backend Developer & DevOps Engineer
My responsibilities	 - Develop APIs for the mobile application - Develop a mobile application in React Native - Design microservice architecture - Setup CI/CD system with Jenkins, Kubernetes, AWS, Ansible, Terraform, Packer, Fabric and Fastlane
Technologies used	- Python, Django, React Js, React Native, Docker

SUPER ENGLISH

(2017 - 2017)

Customer	ICRARY
Description	Learn English online

Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Analysis and designDevelopmentReview codeOptimize codeBug Fixing
Technologies used	- Python, Django

RETRIEVER

(2/2016 - 7/2017)

0 1	OAMOUNO MODUE OFFITED
Customer	SAMSUNG MOBILE CENTER
Description	This is the system that helps project leader manage project very good.
Team size	5
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Analysis and design- Development- Review code- Optimize code- Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- Django, React.js

AUTOPOST

(2014 - 2014)

Customer	SOLID
Description	The software automatically posted ads
Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	Analysis and designDevelopmentReview codeOptimize codeBug Fixing
Technologies used	- C#

AUTO SCAN EMAIL, MOBILE NUMBER

(2013 - 2014)

Customer	SOLID
Description	This is app can collect all mobile number, email address from any website.
Team size	2
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Analysis and design - Development - Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	C#

RESTAURANT MANAGEMENT

(2012 - 2013)

Customer	DCOS

Description	This is app that helps manager restaurant easy.
Team size	8
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Optimize code - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	C#, Asp.net